Finding Aid for the Getty Research Institute Scholars Program Images and Recordings, 1985-2013 IA20026
Institutional Records and Archives
- Photographs, 1985-2007; Series III.; 31.85 Linear Feet (33 boxes)
  - Scholar portraits: contact sheets, negatives, and photograhic prints, 1985-2007; 30.75 Linear Feet (31 boxes)
    - 1986-1987:
      - Scholar Program people and activities
        - Pierre Boulez Luncheon (Box 1995.IA.02-2, Folder 6)
        - Dutch Studies Symposium (Box 1995.IA.02-2, Folder 7)
        - Patronage Symposium (Box 1995.IA.02-2, Folder 8)
    - 1987-1988:
      - Scholars and fellows
        - Svetlana Alpers (Box 1995.IA.02-2, Folder 14)
        - Marcia Ascher (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 1)
        - Antonio Bonet-Correa (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 2)
        - Jacqueline Burkhardt (Box 1995.IA.02-2, Folder 13)
        - Caroline Bynum (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 3)
        - Bill Christian (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 4)
        - Charles Dill (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 5)
        - Gisele Freund (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 6)
        - Wolfgang Kemp (Box 1995.IA.02-2, Folder 9)
        - Martin Lowry (Box 1995.IA.02-2, Folder 10)
        - Sheldon Nodelman (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 8)
        - Conrad Rudolph (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 9)
        - Carl Schorske (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 10)
        - Daniel Selden (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 11)
        - Leo Steinberg (Box 1995.IA.02-2, Folder 12)
        - Marina Warner (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 12)
      - Scholar Program people and activities
        - Lowry Lecture/Reception (Box 1995.IA.02-2, Folder 11)
        - Freund Film (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 7)
        - Dewe-Matthews Exhibition (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 13)
        - Architectural Tour (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 14)
        - Frank Gehry Day (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 15)
        - Conservation Institute (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 16)
        - Forster Garden Party (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 17)
        - Scholar Party, June 5, 1988 (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 18)
        - Center Architecture (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 19)
        - 7th Floor, Moving Day (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 20)
        - Herb Hymans and Mary [unknown last name] Birthday Party (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 21)
        - Christmas Card, 1987 (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 22)
        - Tom Reese (and family) (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 23)
        - Nicholas Olsberg (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 24)
        - Gene Hamilton (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 25)
        - Michelle [illegible last name] (Box 1995.IA.02-3, Folder 26)
    - 1988-1989:
      - Scholars and fellows
        - Joseph Auner (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 1)
        - George Baird (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 2)
        - François Bucher (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 3)
        - Tilmann Buddensieg (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 4)
        - John Goody (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 5)
        - Eric Hobsbawn (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 6)
        - Aron Gurevich (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 7)
        - Thomas Huhn (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 8)
        - Anne Gret Janda (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 9)
        - Christiane Klapisch (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 10)
        - George Kubler (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 11)
        - Harry Mallgrave (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 12)
        - George Marcus (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 13)
        - Raymonde Moulin (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 14)
        - Fritz Neumeyer (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 15)
        - Lauren O'Connell (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 16)
        - Robert Piencikowski (Box 1995.IA.02-4, Folder 17)
        - Ulrich Schneider (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 1)
        - Salvatore Settis (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 2)
        - George Stocking (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 3)
        - Elizabeth Watson (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 4)
      - Scholar program people and activities
        - Scholar Reception, Reese Home, October 15, 1988 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 5)
        - Scholar Informal Discussion, January 25, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 6)
        - Lecture: C. Garcia-Rodero and B. Christian (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 7)
        - Seminar: John Onians, April 19, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 8)
        - Scholar Informal Discussion, February 22, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 9)
        - Scholar Informal Discussion, March 8, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 10)
        - Scholar Informal Discussion, April 13, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 11)
        - Center Piece: Minorities American Art, April 21, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 12)
        - Wagner Symposium, November 3-5, 1988 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 13)
        - Wagner Symposium [continued], November 3-5, 1988 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 14)
        - Center Christmas Party, 1988 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 15)
        - Scholar Christmas Lunch, December 21, 1988 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 16)
        - Birthday Party, Herb Hymans and Mary [illegible last name: may be Llewenyn?], January 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 17)
        - Otto Wittmann (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 18)
        - Fred Bohrer (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 19)
        - Staff (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 20)
        - Staff: Miscellaneous (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 21)
        - Christmas Card, 1988 (Box 1995.IA.02-5, Folder 22)
    - 1989-1990:
      - Scholars and fellows
        - Luigi Ballerini (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 1)
        - Stephen Barthelmess (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 2)
        - Yve-Alain Bois (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 3)
        - Ian Boyd Whyte (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 4)
        - Mary Ann Caws (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 5)
        - Albrecht Dumling (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 6)
        - Luis Fernández-Galiano (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 7)
        - James Herbert (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 8)
        - W. Herrmann (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 9)
        - Peter Jelavich and Ellen Handler Spitz (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 10)
        - Anton Kaes (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 11)
        - Claude Keisch (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 12)
        - Klaus Kropfinger (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 13)
        - Sylvia Lavin (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 14)
        - H. Mallgrave, 1990 (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 15)
        - Annette Michelson (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 16)
        - Kenneth Silver (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 17)
        - Yvonne Spielmann (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 18)
        - Nancy Troy (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 19)
        - Peg Weiss (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 20)
        - Beat Wyss (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 21)
      - Scholar program people and activities
        - David Antin Lecture (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 22)
        - A. Boyarsky Lecture, November 3, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-6, Folder 23)
        - Maria Phillips Lecture (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 1)
        - Berlin Roundtable, December 13, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 2)
        - Romanian Roundtable (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 3)
        - L.A. Tour, October 21, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 4)
        - Architectural Tour (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 5)
        - Scholar Reception, September 20, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 6)
        - Scholar Reception #2, October 10, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 7)
        - Forster Garden Party, October 15, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 8)
        - Christmas Card and Mary [unknown last name] farewell, October 5, 1989 (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 10)
          Includes three single negative strips labeled "Smokers", "Staff", and [illegible]
    - 1990-1991:
      - Scholars and fellows
        - Oskar Batschmann (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 11)
        - Suzanne Blier (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 12)
        - Vittode Branca (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 13)
        - Luisa Ciammitti (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 14)
        - Johannes Fabian (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 15)
        - Ursela Frohne (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 16)
        - Teresa Gisbert (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 17)
        - Keith Holz (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 18)
        - Stephan von Huene and Petra Kipphoff (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 3)
        - Sanford Kwinter (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 19)
        - Mogens Larsen (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 2)
        - Tom Levin (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 21)
        - Sabine MacCormack (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 22)
        - Ákos Moranvánsky (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 23)
        - Andrew Stewart (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 24)
        - Mario Torelli (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 1)
        - Hayden White (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 4)
        - Tom Zuidema (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 5)
      - Scholar program people and activities
        - Gehry/Holl Lecture (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 20)
        - Frank Gehry (Box 1995.IA.02-7, Folder 25)
          No proofs and negatives are in this file: only a call slip for 13 contact prints and 45 negative strips.
        - Salvatore Settis Lecture (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 6)
        - Hymans Centerpiece (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 7)
        - L.A. Tour (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 8)
        - Garden Party (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 9)
        - Christmas Party (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 10)
        - Christmas Card (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous/Staff (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 12)
    - 1991-1992:
      - Scholars and fellows
        - Elliott Carter (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 13)
        - David Cairns (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 14)
        - Aris Fioretos (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 15)
        - Lynn Garafola (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 16)
        - William Gass (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 17)
        - Neil Harris (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 18)
        - Mikhail Iampolski (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 19)
        - Ursula Pia Jauch (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 20)
        - Barbara Kirshenblatt-Gimblett (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 21)
        - Gàbor Klaniczay (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 22)
        - Jose Luis Mateo (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 23)
        - Keith Moxey (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 24)
        - Werner Oechslin (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 25)
        - Peter Pozefsky (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 26)
        - Juan-Antonio Ramirez (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 27)
        - Joseph Rykwert (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 28)
        - Birgit Verwiebe (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 29)
        - Anthony Vidler (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 1)
        - Richard Wollheim (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 2)
        - Brigitte Werneburg (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 3)
      - Scholar program people and activities
        - Lynn Garafola (publicity) and Birgit Verwiebe lecture (Box 1995.IA.02-8, Folder 30)
        - L.A. Tour (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 4)
        - Scholar Reception (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 5)
        - Scholar Reception #2 (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 6)
        - Garden Party (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 7)
        - Christmas Party (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 8)
        - Christmas Card (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 9)
        - Scholar Retreat (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 10)
        - [Shoenberg?] Symposium (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 11)
        - [Shoenberg?] Symposium [continued] (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 12)
        - Street Art/Graffiti Vandalism (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 13)
        - Street Art/Graffiti Vandalism [continued] (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 14)
        - Neutra Symposium (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 15)
    - 1992-1993:
      - Scholars and fellows
        - Thomas Bender and Gwendolyn Wright (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 16)
        - Ruth Ben-Ghiat (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 17)
        - Adolf Borbein (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 18)
        - Charles Burnett (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 19)
        - Jean-Louis Cohen (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 20)
        - Marco de Michelis (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 21)
        - Essex Hemphill (Box 1995.IA.02-9, Folder 22)
        - Klaus Herding (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 1)
        - Robert Hullot-Kentor (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 2)
        - Nicholas Largier (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 3)
        - György Ligeti (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 4)
        - George Lipsitz (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 5)
        - Jennie Livingston (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 6)
        - Patricia Morton (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 7)
        - Margaret Nesbit (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 8)
        - Katherine Rudolph (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 9)
        - Lisa Tiersten (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 10)
        - Stanislaus von Moos (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 11)
        - Michael Wintroub (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 12)
        - Irving Wohlfarth (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 13)
        - Christa Wolf (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 14)
      - Scholar program people and activites
        - L.A. Tour (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 15)
        - Welcome reception and reception #2 (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 16)
        - Informal Scholar Discussion (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 17)
    - 1993-1994:
      - Scholars and fellows
        - Joan Branham (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 18)
        - Darrell Davis (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 19)
        - Pierre Duviols (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 20)
        - Diana Fane (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 21)
        - Enrique Florescano (Box 1995.IA.02-10, Folder 22)
        - Graziano Gasparini (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 1)
        - Ramón Gutiérrez (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 2)
        - Margarita Gutman (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 3)
        - Lewis Hyde (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 4)
        - Jorge Klor de Alva (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 5)
        - Heather Lechtman (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 6)
        - John Loomis (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 7)
        - Robbie McCauley (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 8)
        - Natalie Melas (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 9)
        - Rosamund Purcell (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 10)
        - Paul Raabe (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 11)
        - Mario Sartor (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 12)
        - Bernhard Schimmelpfennig (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 13)
        - Allan Sekula (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 14)
        - John Yau (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 15)
      - Scholar program people and activites
        - Tom Reese Lecture (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 16)
        - Salvatore Settis Address (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 17)
        - L.A. Tour (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 18)
        - Brentwood Tour (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 19)
        - Museum Tour (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 20)
        - Welcome Reception (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 21)
        - Miscellaneous/Staff (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 22)
        - Christmas Party (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 23)
        - Mel Edelstein acquisitions talk (Box 1995.IA.02-11, Folder 24)
    - 1994-1995:
      - Julia Annas (Box 1995.IA.02-12, Folder 1)
      - Aleida Assmann (Box 1995.IA.02-12, Folder 2)
      - Jan Assmann (Box 1995.IA.02-12, Folder 3)
      - Michael Baxandall (Box 1995.IA.02-12, Folder 4)
      - Mary Carruthers (Box 1995.IA.02-12, Folder 5)
      - Chad Coerver (Box 1995.IA.02-12, Folder 6)
      - Mark Franko (Box 1995.IA.02-12, Folder 7)
      - Carlo Ginzburg (Box 1995.IA.02-12, Folder 8)
      - Stuart Harten (Box 1995.IA.02-12, Folder 9)
      - Francois Hartog (Box 1995.IA.02-12, Folder 10)
      - Claude Imbert (Box 1995.IA.02-13, Folder 1)
      - Christian Jacob (Box 1995.IA.02-13, Folder 2)
      - Karen Kettering (Box 1995.IA.02-13, Folder 3)
      - Heiner Muller (Box 1995.IA.02-13, Folder 4)
      - Krzystof Pomian (Box 1995.IA.02-13, Folder 5)
      - Jacques Revel (Box 1995.IA.02-13, Folder 6)
      - Charles Rhyne (Box 1995.IA.02-13, Folder 7)
      - Annette Richards (Box 1995.IA.02-13, Folder 8)
      - Michael Roth (Box 1995.IA.02-13, Folder 9)
      - Carlo Severi (Box 1995.IA.02-14, Folder 1)
      - Susan Sontag (Box 1995.IA.02-14, Folder 2)
      - Richard Sorabji (Box 1995.IA.02-14, Folder 3)
      - Randolph Starn (Box 1995.IA.02-14, Folder 4)
      - Susan Stewart (Box 1995.IA.02-14, Folder 5)
      - Guillermo Vazquez Consuegra (Box 1995.IA.02-14, Folder 6)
      - Nathan Wachtel (Box 1995.IA.02-14, Folder 7)
    - 1995-1996:
      - Harrison Birtwistle (Box 1995.IA.02-14, Folder 8)
      - Paula Findlen (Box 1995.IA.02-14, Folder 9)
      - Enrique Florescano (Box 2006.IA.24-1, Folder 1)
      - Saul Friedlander (Box 1995.IA.02-14, Folder 10)
      - Todd Gernes (Box 1995.IA.02-15, Folder 1)
      - Francis Haskell (Box 1995.IA.02-15, Folder 2)
      - Henri Lavagne D'Ortigue (Box 1995.IA.02-15, Folder 3)
      - William MacGregor (Box 1995.IA.02-15, Folder 4)
      - Jenifer Neils (Box 1995.IA.02-15, Folder 5)
      - Shigetoshi Osano (Box 1995.IA.02-15, Folder 6)
      - Pratapaditya Pal (Box 1995.IA.02-15, Folder 7)
      - Giuseppe Pucci (Box 1995.IA.02-15, Folder 8)
      - Carlos Sambricio (Box 1995.IA.02-15, Folder 9)
      - Alain Schnapp (Box 1995.IA.02-16, Folder 1)
      - Aaron Segal (Box 1995.IA.02-16, Folder 2)
      - Barbara Stafford (Box 1995.IA.02-16, Folder 3)
    - 1996-1997:
      - Brenda Bright (Box 1995.IA.02-16, Folder 4)
      - Robert Carringer (Box 1995.IA.02-16, Folder 5)
      - Bernard Cooper (Box 1995.IA.02-16, Folder 6)
      - Dorothy Crawford (Box 1995.IA.02-16, Folder 7)
      - Robert Dawidoff (Box 1995.IA.02-16, Folder 8)
      - Bill Deverell (Box 1995.IA.02-17, Folder 1)
      - Christopher Donnan (Box 1995.IA.02-17, Folder 2)
      - Philip Ethington (Box 1995.IA.02-17, Folder 3)
      - Robbert Flick (Box 1995.IA.02-17, Folder 4)
      - Roger Friedland (Box 1995.IA.02-17, Folder 5)
      - Paolo Gasparini (Box 1995.IA.02-17, Folder 6)
      - Kanishka Goonewardena (Box 1995.IA.02-17, Folder 7)
      - Thomas Hines (Box 1995.IA.02-17, Folder 8)
      - David James (Box 1995.IA.02-18, Folder 1)
      - Samella Lewis (Box 1995.IA.02-18, Folder 2)
      - Jerome Monnet (Box 1995.IA.02-18, Folder 3)
      - Becky Nicolaides (Box 1995.IA.02-18, Folder 4)
      - Carolyn See (Box 1995.IA.02-18, Folder 5)
      - Allan Sekula (Box 1995.IA.02-18, Folder 6)
      - RJ Smith (Box 1995.IA.02-18, Folder 7)
      - Raul Villa (Box 1995.IA.02-18, Folder 8)
    - 1997-1999:
      - Norman Bryson (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 1)
      - Page Dubois (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 2)
      - Martha Feldman (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 3)
      - Philip Fisher (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 4)
      - Diego Lanza (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 5)
      - Reinhart Meyer-Kalkus (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 6)
      - Adrian M. S. Piper (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 7)
      - Nicola Savarese (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 8)
      - Elaine Scarry (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 9)
      - Debora Silverman (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 10)
      - Lesley Stern (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 11)
      - David Summers (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 12)
      - Bill Viola (Box 2006.IA.24-2, Folder 13)
    - 1999-2000:
      - Scholars
        - Photograph releases (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 1)
        - Test @ grade 2, 1997-2000 (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 2)
          [19 4"x4.5" prints representing a sample of scholars.]
        - Final scholars, 1999-2000 (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 3)
          [19 3"x4" prints]
        - David Carrier (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 4)
        - Timothy James Clark (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 5)
        - Heinrich Dilly (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 6)
        - Lydia Goehr (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 7)
        - Thomas DaCosta Kaufmann (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 8)
        - Donata Levi (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 9)
        - Robert S. Nelson (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 10)
        - Margaret R. Olin (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 11)
        - Ernst Osterkamp (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 12)
        - Erika Rummel (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 13)
        - Elizabeth Sears (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 14)
        - Catherine M. Soussloff (Box 2006.IA.24-3, Folder 15)
      - Pre- and post-doctoral
        - Photo releases (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 1)
        - Elspeth Brown (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 2)
        - Darcy Buerkle (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 3)
        - Francesco de Angelis (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 4)
        - Otniel Dror (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 5)
        - Andreas Gailus (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 6)
        - Stefan Jonsson (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 7)
        - Juliet Koss (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 8)
        - Elizabeth Liebman (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 9)
        - Richard Meyer (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 10)
        - Margaret Pagaduan (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 11)
        - Linda-Anne Rebhun (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 12)
        - Catherine Schaller (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 13)
        - Meng Yue (Box 2006.IA.24-4, Folder 14)
    - 2000-2001:
      - Malcolm Baker (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 1)
      - Mario Carpo (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 2)
      - Whitney Davis (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 3)
      - Peter Forgacs (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 4)
      - Dorinne Kondo (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 5)
      - Lothar Ledderose (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 6)
      - Sherrie Levine (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 7)
      - Partha Mitter (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 8)
      - Joost van Oss (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 9)
      - Ingrid Rowland (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 10)
      - Pamela Smith (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 11)
      - Anne Wagner (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 12)
      - Herta Wolf (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 13)
      - Rani Singh (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 14)
      - Michael Lobel (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 15)
      - Alastair Wright (Box 2006.IA.24-5, Folder 16)
    - 2001-2002:
      - Mieke Bal (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 1)
      - S. M. Can Bilsel (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 2)
      - Benjamin Buchloh (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 3)
      - Charles Harrison (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 4)
      - Melissa Hyde (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 5)
      - John Hyman (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 6)
      - Kajri Jain (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 7)
      - Lawrence Kruger (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 8)
      - Jacqueline Lichtenstein (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 9)
      - Maria Hsiuya Loh (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 10)
      - Jerry Moore (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 11)
      - Deanna Petherbridge (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 12)
      - Lisa Pon (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 13)
      - Dennis L. Sepper (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 14)
      - Terence E. Smith (Box 2006.IA.24-6, Folder 15)
    - 2002-2003:
      - Dympa Callaghan (Box 2006.IA.24-7, Folder 1)
      - Bruno Chenique (Box 2006.IA.24-7, Folder 2)
      - Janet Hoskins (Box 2006.IA.24-7, Folder 3)
      - Pat Kirkham (Box 2006.IA.24-7, Folder 4)
      - Kate Nicholson (Box 2006.IA.24-7, Folder 5)
      - Rudolf Preimesberger (Box 2006.IA.24-7, Folder 6)
      - Robert Rosenstone (Box 2006.IA.24-7, Folder 7)
      - Sally Stein (Box 2006.IA.24-7, Folder 8)
      - Dieter Thomae (Box 2006.IA.24-7, Folder 9)
      - Jonathan Weimberg (Box 2006.IA.24-7, Folder 10)
      - Photo collage of scholars (Box 2006.IA.24-7, Folder 11)
    - 2003-2004:
      - Getty Scholars
        - Malcolm Bull (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 1)
        - Ting Chang (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 2)
        - Serge Guilbaut (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 3)
        - Robert Jensen (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 4)
        - Carol Knicely (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 5)
        - Miwon Kwon (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 6)
        - Mark Meadow (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 7)
        - Rochelle Ziskin (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 8)
      - Predoctoral Fellows
        - A. Cassandra Albinson (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 9)
        - Christopher Heuer (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 10)
        - Matthew Jackson (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 11)
        - Tatiana Senkevitch (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 12)
        - Isabelle Tillerot (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 13)
        - Sebastian Zeidler (Box 2006.IA.24-8, Folder 14)
    - 2004-2005:
      - Getty Scholars
        - Tim Barringer (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 1)
        - Howard Bloch (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 2)
        - Joan Landes (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 3)
        - Sylvia Lavin (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 4)
        - Thomas Levin (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 5)
        - P. Adams Sitney (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 6)
      - Predoctoral Fellows
        - Carrie Nakamura (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 7)
        - Vimalin Rujivacharakul (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 8)
        - Minou Schraven (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 9)
        - Michael Schreyach (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 10)
      - Postdoctoral Fellows